

Personal

- Name
 Ahmet Furkan Kuyular
- Address Hurriyet mahallesi adilhan sokak, Number: 8 34600 Kagıthane
- Phone number 05550358124
- Email furkankuyular@yahoo.com
- **Date of birth** 21-06-1997
- Place of birth Beyoğlu
- Gender

 Male
- Nationality
 Muaf
- Marital status
 Bekar
- Driving licence
- LinkedIn

 https://www.linkedin.com/in/furkar

 kuyular-9591a8183/

Interests

- Reading News
- Walking
- Camping
- Watching Sports

AHMET FURKAN KUYULAR

Hello, I'm Furkan, I was born on 21 June 1997. I am a graduate of Pamukkale University Computer Programming Department, I have 5 years of experience in the software industry. I started my career with the Salesforce CRM application. I am currently working as a PHP developer. I have experience with Symfony and Laravel. I have taken part in important projects by adapting to the teams I have been in until now. I pay a lot of attention to writing clean code and the architecture on the code.

Thank You. Regards,



Work experience

Sep 2016 - Jul 2016

Intern

Akdora Software & Consulting, İstanbul

Jun 2018 - Aug 2018

Intern

Linus Consulting Service, İstanbul

May 2019

Backend Developer

Bircom Telecommunication and Information Services Inc., İstanbul

- PHP Developer
- - B2B ve B2C structures integration operations
- · CRM, Shopify, Wordpress integration operations

•

- Technologies: PHP, Symfony, Salesforce, REST API, SOAP API, PHP MVC, Apex Classes, Batch Apex Classes, Apex Triggers, Informatica, Callipso Enterprise Analyze, MSSQL, SOQL, Bitbucket, Jira, Git, PHPstorm, Graylog, Redis, ElasticSearch, RabbitMQ(amqp), Swagger UI
- Websites: www.hifilife.com, www.sennheiser.com, www.kulaklik.com, www.telkomarket.com, www.kazananbayi.com, www.bircom.com, www.hepsiburada.com, www.n11.com, www.trendyol.com,
- B2B ve B2C structures integration operations CRM,Shopify,Wordpress integration operations Technologies:
 PHP, Symfony, Salesforce, REST API, SOAP API, PHP MVC,
 Apex Classes, Batch Apex Classes, Apex Triggers, Informatica,
 Callipso Enterprise Analyze, MSSQL, SOQL, Bitbucket, Jira,
 Git, PHPstorm, Graylog, Redis, ElasticSearch,
 RabbitMQ(amqp), Swagger UI Websites: www.hifilife.com,
 www.sennheiser.com, www.kulaklik.com,
 www.telkomarket.com, www.kazananbayi.com,
 www.trendyol.com, www.hepsiburada.com, www.n11.com,
 www.trendyol.com, www.gittigidiyor.com

 Customer Relationship Management Administrator and Developer

- · Istanbul, Turkey
- Istanbul, Turkey
- Salesforce Administrator
- -Salesforce Developer

www.gittigidiyor.com

Jun 2022 - Oct 2022

Senior PHP Developer

Experilabs by SAHABT Software, İstanbul

Senior PHP developer:

- Laravel
- Standalone project creation and development
- Using patterns and writing with clean code

Oct 2023 - Present Se

Senior PHP Developer

ONT Information Technology Trade Inc., Istanbul

Laravel Framework,

- Request Classes
- Response Resources,
- ValueObjects
- Events, Listeners, Observers, Jobs
- Queues
- ETC.
- Laravel Dumps

Nginx,

Mysql,

Redis,

CRM and CMS monolith projects,

Javascript - Jquery, Datatables

Sentry,

IDE:And Programs

PhpStorm,

DataGrip,

Postman,

Teams, Discord,



Education and Qualifications

Sep 2016 - Jul 2018

Ön Lisans Mezunu

Pamukkale University, İstanbul

 $\star\star\star\star\star$



Skills

SOAP API

Symfony	****
Laravel	****
Redis	****
ElasticSearch	****
RabbitMQ	****
Git	****
PhpStorm	****
Postman	****
Swagger UI	****
Java	****
Salesforce Administrator	****
Salesforce Developer	****
Mysql, Mssql, Soql	****
REST API	****

BitBucket

Jira

Graylog

C#

Apex - Classess, Triggers, Batch Apex

Sentry

★★★★★

★★★★★



References

eQuota

Harun Memur
0531 857 10 65

Cue Health

Müşerref Sefer
0539 469 42 62

Hitit

Oğuz Kocaman
0507 084 66 58

Misli

Yağmur Aman
0539 971 41 15

ONT Information
Technology Trade Inc.

Onur Simsek

posta@onursimsek.com